Indiana University President's Office records, 1937-1962 C213
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1937-1962
  - Bar, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 60)
  - Bardwell, E. P., 1944-1962; (10 Files) (Box 60)
  - Bark, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 60)
  - Barker, Dean C. W. (Box 60)
  - Barker, C. W. Acting Dean, 1938-1940; (2 folders) (Box 60)
  - Barker, Morris C., 1946-1947; (2 folders) (Box 60)
  - Barker, Morris C., 1948-1957; (9 folders) (Box 61)
  - Barn, 1937-1955; (12 folders) (Box 61)
  - Barr, 1937-1948; (11 folders) (Box 61)
  - Barr, 1947-1962; (14 folders) (Box 62)
  - Bart, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 62)
  - Bartley, E. Ross, 1937-1962; (31 folders) (Box 62)
  - Bas, 1937-1962; (24 folders) (Box 63)
  - Baseball (Professional), 1943 (Box 63)
  - Baseball Schedule, I.U., 1937-1938 (Box 63)
  - Base Hospital 32, 1941-1942 (Box 63)
  - Basketball Prospectus and Basketball Miscellaneous, 1939-1943; (2 folders) (Box 63)
  - Basketball, 1950-1960; (55 folders) (Box 63)
  - Basketball, 1959-1962; (15 folders) (Box 64)
  - Big Ten Business Officers Conference, 1962 (Box 64)
  - Bat, 1937-1960; (18 folders) (Box 64)
  - Bates, Robert, 1945-1947; (2 folders) (Box 64)
  - Bath, Thomas E. (Box 64)
  - Bau, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 64)
  - Bay, 1937-1955; (18 folders) (Box 64)
  - Be, 1938-1941; (3 folders) (Box 64)
  - Be, 1941-1962; (14 folders) (Box 65)
  - Bea, 1947-1955; (8 folders) (Box 65)
  - Beauchamp, Dr. George E., 1950-1951 (Box 65)
  - Bec, 1937-1951; (14 folders) (Box 65)
  - Bec, 1951-1962; (11 folders) (Box 66)
  - Beck, Dr. Frank O. (Box 66)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 66)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 66)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 66)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 66)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 66)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 66)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 66)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 66)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 66)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 66)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 66)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 66)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 66)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 66)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 66)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 66)
    - 1958-1962 (Box 66)
  - Beck Chapel, 1941-1962 (Box 66)
  - Becowitz, Mr. and Mrs. Louis, 1941-1954 (Box 66)
  - Bed, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 66)
  - Bedford Junior College, 1957-1958 (Box 66)
  - Bee, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 66)
  - Begdes, Kutsi, 1939-1957 (Box 66)
  - Beh, 1941-1947; (4 folders) (Box 66)
  - Behrendt, Richard F., 1939-1941; (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Bel, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 66)
  - Ben, 1937-1942; (5 folders) (Box 66)
  - Ben, 1942-1962; (20 folders) (Box 67)
  - Benes, Vaclav, 1950-1962 (Box 67)
  - Benn, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 67)
  - Bennett, Orval, 1937-1938 (Box 67)
  - Bens, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 67)
  - Bensinger, Merle Howard, 1943-1944 (Box 67)
  - Benton, Thomas Hart - Murals (Box 67)
    - 1939 (Box 67)
    - 1940-1959 (Box 67)
  - Ber, 1937-1951; (14 folders) (Box 67)
  - Ber, 1951-1962; (11 folders) (Box 68)
  - Berg, 1949-1955; (6 folders) (Box 68)
  - Bergevin, Paul, 1947-1961 (Box 68)
  - Bern, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 68)
  - Berndt, A. H. Safety Department, 1938-1948; (10 folders) (Box 68)
  - Berr, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 68)
  - Berry, Cecelia Ray (2 folders) (Box 68)
  - Berry, Lillian Gay, 1941-1943; (2 folders) (Box 68)
  - Bes, 1937-1962; (24 folders) (Box 68)
  - Bet, 1946-1947 (Box 68)
  - Beta Gamma Sigma, 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 68)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 1939-1959 (Box 68)
  - Better Management Roundtable, 1955-1956 (Box 68)
  - Bevington-Williams, Inc., 1937-1940; (4 folders) (Box 68)
  - Bi, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 69)
  - Biarritz American University, 1945-1946 (Box 69)
  - Biddle, Ward G., 1937-1938; (8 folders) (Box 69)
  - Biddle, Ward G., 1937-1940; (32 folders) (Box 70)
  - Biddle, Ward G., 1940-1943; (31 folders) (Box 71)
  - Biddle, Ward G. (Box 72)
  - Bibliography, 1943-1944 (Box 72)
  - Bie, 1947-1948 (Box 72)
  - Big, 1937-1940; (3 folders) (Box 72)
  - Big Ten Business Officer Conference, 1941-1954; (5 folders) (Box 72)
  - Big Ten, 1954-1958; (12 folders) (Box 72)
  - Big Ten, 1958-1962; (11 folders) (Box 73)
  - Bil, 1953-1955; (2 folders) (Box 73)
  - Bin, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 73)
  - Biochemists (Box 73)
  - Biological Station, 1956-1962 (Box 73)
  - Biology Department Applicants (Box 73)
  - Biology Institute, 1956 (Box 73)
  - Biology Survey Course, 1939-1940 (Box 73)
  - Bir, 1953-1955; (2 folders) (Box 73)
  - Biraud, Frances, 1943-1944 (Box 73)
  - Bis, 1937-1949; (5 folders) (Box 73)
  - Bittner, W. S., 1937-1953; (21 folders) (Box 73)
  - Bl, 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 73)
  - Bl, 1943-1962; (19 folders) (Box 74)
  - Bla, 1947-1948 (Box 74)
  - Blac, 1949-1955; (6 folders) (Box 74)
  - Black, 1946-1947 (Box 74)
  - Black, C. J. Purchasing Agent, 1938-1955; (15 folders) (Box 74)
  - Blackwell, Raymond E., 1938-1942 (Box 74)
  - Blai, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 74)
  - Blak, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 74)
  - Blake, Mildred B., 1941-1955 (Box 74)
  - Blas, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 74)
  - Blind-Research work for, 1939-1940 (Box 74)
  - Blind Students, Readers, 1945-1947; (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - Blo, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 75)
  - Bloomington, Miscellaneous, 1941-1962; (20 folders) (Box 75)
  - Bloomington Advancement Association, 1953-1954 (Box 75)
  - Bloomington Business and Professional Leaders, 1957 (Box 75)
  - Bloomington Chamber of Commerce, 1938-1953; (15 folders) (Box 75)
  - Bloomington Chamber of Commerce, 1953-1962; (9 folders) (Box 76)
  - Bloomington Community Chest, 1952-1960; (7 folders) (Box 76)
  - Bloomington County Club, 1954-1962; (8 folders) (Box 76)
  - Bloomington Fire Truck (Box 76)
  - Bloomington Hospital, 1937-1962; (9 folders) (Box 76)
  - Bloomington Campaign Executive Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 76)
  - Bloomington IN Recreation Survey, 1956-1957 (Box 76)
  - Bloomington Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1938-1943; (5 folders) (Box 76)
  - Bloomington Kiwanis Club, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 76)
  - Bloomington Mayor, 1949-1954; (4 folders) (Box 76)
  - Bloomington Human Relations Commission, 1951-1952 (Box 76)
  - Bloomington Meeting with Mayor Lemon, 3 FebConfidential, 1956 (Box 76)
  - Bloomington National Bank, 1945-1962; (17 folders) (Box 77)
  - Bloomington Rotary Club, 1938-1962; (24 folders) (Box 77)
  - Bloomington Water Mains, Sewers, Sewer and Water Rates, 1946-1951; (3 folders) (Box 77)
  - Bloomington Water Rates, 1950-1951; (7 folders) (Box 77)
  - Bloomington Street Department Street Repairs, 1946-1952; (7 folders) (Box 77)
  - Bloomington United Fund, 1955-1962; (9 folders) (Box 77)
  - Bloomington Waterworks, 1951-1952 (Box 77)
  - Blu, 1948-1950; (2 folders) (Box 77)
  - Blue Cross Hospital Service, 1944-1945 (Box 77)
  - Blue Cross-Blue Shield Hospitalization Insurance, 1949-1960; (12 folders) (Box 77)
  - Blue Cross-Blue Shield Hospitalization Insurance, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 78)
  - Blue Key, 1939-1949; (9 folders) (Box 78)
  - Bo, 1937-1960; (21 folders) (Box 78)
  - Bo, 1960-1962; (3 folders) (Box 79)
  - Board for Fundamental Education, 1955-1960; (7 folders) (Box 79)
  - Board Papers-Miscellaneous, 1937-1956; (19 folders) (Box 79)
  - Board of Trustees I.U., 1946-1957; (21 folders) (Box 79)
  - Brosius Camp BOT Meeting July 3 to 5, 1942 (Box 79)
  - Brosius Camp Notices, 1957-1958 (Box 79)
  - Brosius Camp Room Appointments, 1957-1958 (Box 79)
  - Bot, 1958-1962; (17 folders) (Box 79)
  - Boardman, Martha J. (Box 79)
  - Bockstahler, O.L. (Box 79)
  - Bockstahler, Prof. O.L. Case (Box 80)
  - Bobbs Menill Company, 1949-1952; (3 folders) (Box 80)
  - Boe, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 80)
  - Bogart, Paul, 1938-1940; (2 folders) (Box 80)
  - Boh, 1941-1962; (19 folders) (Box 80)
  - Bohlen, D.A. & Son, 1937-1938 (Box 80)
  - Boisen, Anton, 1938 (Box 80)
  - Bol, 1937-1955; (12 folders) (Box 80)
  - Bolt, Don, 1957-1958 (Box 80)
  - Bon, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 80)
  - Bond, Florence, July, 1937 (Box 80)
  - Bonds, 1938-1962; (28 folders) (Box 80)
  - Bonsib, Louis W., 1937-1938 (Box 80)
  - Bonds, Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 81)
  - Boo, 1942-1955; (13 folders) (Box 81)
  - Booz, Allen Aid Hamilton, 1962 (Box 81)
  - Book Collector's Contest, 1951-1952 (Box 81)
  - Book Nook, 1938 (Box 81)
  - Books (Council on Books in War-Time) (Box 81)
  - Books-Advertisements-For Sale, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 81)
  - Books-Received and Returned, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 81)
  - Books to be Read, 1938-1943; (5 folders) (Box 81)
  - Bookstore, 1937-1955; (24 folders) (Box 81)
  - Bookstore, 1955-1962; (21 folders) (Box 82)
  - I.U. Bookstore Annual Reports, 1937-1962; (23 folders) (Box 82)
  - Bor, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 82)
  - The Bored Walk, 1938-1943 (Box 82)
  - Bos, 1937-1946; (9 folders) (Box 82)
  - Bos, 1946-1962; (16 folders) (Box 83)
  - Botany Dept Applications (Box 83)
  - Bou, 1937-1950; (6 folders) (Box 83)
  - Bow, 1937-1962; (24 folders) (Box 83)
  - Bowen, Donald, 1959-1960 (Box 83)
  - Bowie, Theodore, 1950-1961 (Box 83)
  - Bowling Green State University, 1943-1944 (Box 83)
  - Bowman, Sylvia (Box 83)
  - Boy, 1937-1955; (13 folders) (Box 83)
  - Boy Scout Troop 83 Indianapolis, 1946-1947 (Box 83)
  - Boy Scout Day at I.U., 1938-1939 (Box 83)
  - Boys-President, 1939-1940 (Box 83)
  - Wells should see any other information re, Students Boys, 1937-1938 (Box 83)
  - Br, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 84)
  - Brace, Armin F. Case of, 1937-1938 (Box 84)
  - Brad, 1949-1955; (6 folders) (Box 84)
  - Braden, Samuel E., 1959-1962; (5 folders) (Box 84)
  - Bradford Estate, 1942-1945; (3 folders) (Box 84)
  - Bradford Woods (Box 84)
  - Bradford Woods Annual Report, 1956-1960; (4 folders) (Box 84)
  - Bradfute Building (2 folders) (Box 84)
  - Brai, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 84)
  - Bran, 1941-1950; (9 folders) (Box 84)
  - Bran, 1950-1962; (12 folders) (Box 85)
  - Bras, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 85)
  - Brazil International Cooperation Administration Contract, 1956-1962; (5 folders) (Box 85)
  - Brazil Chemistry Research Project, 1961-1962 (Box 85)
  - Bray, William G., 1950-1951 (Box 85)
  - Brazil Indiana Brazil Fountain Dedication 26 May, 1956 (Box 85)
  - Bre, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 85)
  - Bren, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 85)
  - Brendel, Otto (Box 85)
    - 1941-1943 (Box 85)
    - 1944-1950 (Box 85)
    - 1951-1953 (Box 85)
    - 1954-1957 (Box 85)
  - Bri, 1937-1948; (11 folders) (Box 85)
  - Bri, 1948-1962; (14 folders) (Box 86)
  - Brin, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 86)
  - Briscoe, Herman T., 1938-1961; (27 folders) (Box 86)
  - Briscoe, Orah Cole, 1940-1952 (Box 86)
  - Bro, 1943-1962; (19 folders) (Box 87)
  - Broadman World War Library (Box 87)
  - Broo, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 87)
  - Broom, John Joseph Willard Jr., 1939-1948 (Box 87)
  - Broshar, Herman, 1960 (Box 87)
  - Brow, 1942-1962; (20 folders) (Box 88)
  - Brown, 1949-1955; (12 folders) (Box 88)
  - Brown, Agnes C. -applicant for Home Economics Position, 1937-1938 (Box 88)
  - Brown County Art Association, 1938-1949; (10 folders) (Box 88)
  - Brown County Art Colony, 1938-1939 (Box 88)
  - Brown County Indiana Museum for Modern Art, 1940 (Box 88)
  - Brown County Land for Sale, 1939-1940 (Box 88)
  - Brown County Playhouse (Box 88)
  - Brown County Poetry Club, 1939-1940 (Box 88)
  - Brown, Francis, 1944-1945 (Box 89)
  - Brown, George H.- RE: Colored Alumni Meeting (Box 89)
  - Brown Geo. W., 1940-1941 (Box 89)
  - Brown University Providence, Rhode Island, 1937-1938 (Box 89)
  - Brown William E., 1944-1949 (Box 89)
  - Browning, Grace, 1945-1951; (7 folders) (Box 89)
  - Browsing Library-Suggestions, 1942-1943; (2 folders) (Box 89)
  - Brownson, Charles B., 1953-1954 (Box 89)
  - Bru, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 89)
  - Brun, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 89)
  - Bry, 1938-1955; (12 folders) (Box 89)
  - Bryan House Furnishings (New), 1956-1957 (Box 89)
  - Bryan, Julian Scott, 1939-1940 (Box 89)
  - Bryan, William Lowe President Emeritus, 1937-1938 (Box 89)
  - Bryan, W.L., 1938-1939 (Box 89)
  - Bryan, Dr. William L., 1939-1940 (Box 89)
  - Bryan, President Emeritus W.L., 1940-1946; (6 folders) (Box 89)
  - Bryan, President Emeritus W.L., 1946-1957; (11 folders) (Box 90)
  - Bryan, W.L. Temp, J. Francis Coote, October 17-18, 1956 (Box 90)
  - Bryan Letters, 1955-1956 (Box 90)
  - Dr. Bryan- Sympathy Notes and Letters, 1955-1956; (2 folders) (Box 90)
  - Bryan Scholarship Fund, 1944-1949; (5 folders) (Box 90)
  - Bryan, W.L. Symposium Dinner, 1939-1940 (Box 90)
  - Bu, 1937-1959; (22 folders) (Box 90)
  - Bu, 1959-1962; (3 folders) (Box 91)
  - Buc, 1940-1955; (5 folders) (Box 91)
  - Buck, Gilbert-Mental Case, 1939-1944 (Box 91)
  - Buck, Gilbert, 1949-1950 (Box 91)
  - Budge t- Things to be considered, 1938-1941; (9 folders) (Box 91)
  - Budget Indiana University Salary Analysis, Actual, 1941-1942-; 1940-1941 (Box 91)
  - Budget Items, 1941-1944; (11 folders) (Box 91)
  - Budget Indiana University Salary Analysis, Actual, 1943-1944-; 1942-1943 (Box 91)
  - Letters of Appreciation, 1943-1944 (Box 91)
  - Budget Biennial Budget Request, 1939-1941 (Box 91)
  - Budget, 1940-1945; (8 folders) (Box 91)
  - Legislature-Material to use, 1945; 1943-1944 (Box 91)
  - Budget, 1944-1945 (Box 91)
  - Budget Supporting Papers, 1944-1945 (Box 92)
  - Budget, 1944-1945 (Box 92)
  - Indiana University Salary Analysis, ActualBudget, 1943-1944; 1944-1945 (Box 92)
  - Budget Presentation, Dec. 21, 1944 (Box 92)
  - Building material used also at Trustees meeting, Sept. 1, 1944 (Box 92)
  - Budget Meeting, August 18, 1944 (Box 92)
  - Budget Indiana University Salary Analysis, Actual, 1944-1945-; 1943-1944 (Box 92)
  - Budget Letters of Appreciation, 1944-1945 (Box 92)
  - Budget Committee and Governor-Building Program Meeting, October 18, 1945 (Box 92)
  - Budget, 1945-1951; (22 folders) (Box 92)
  - Budget Biennial Budget Request, 1948-1949; (5 folders) (Box 93)
  - Budget, 1948-1951; (14 folders) (Box 93)
  - Biennial Budget Request, 1950-1951; (2 folders) (Box 93)
  - Confidential Data for I.U. Formula Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 93)
  - Biennial Budget Request, 1950-1953; (8 folders) (Box 93)
  - Biennial Budget Request, 1950-1953; (13 folders) (Box 94)
  - Budget, 1950-1952; (10 folders) (Box 94)
  - Budget-Indiana University Legislative, 1951-1953; (2 folders) (Box 94)
  - Budget, 1951-1952; (2 folders) (Box 94)
  - Budget Request Division of Adult Education, 1951-1952 (Box 94)
  - Budget, 1951-1955; (10 folders) (Box 94)
  - Notes for Meeting, 1952-1953 (Box 94)
  - Budget, 1952-1953 (Box 94)
  - Requests to Budget Committee, 1951-1953 (Box 94)
  - Budget, 1952-1953; (2 folders) (Box 94)
  - Briscoe's Comments, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Budget, 1952-1955; (5 folders) (Box 95)
  - SAB Wells, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Legislature, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Budget, 1953-1955; (6 folders) (Box 95)
  - Education, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Education Building Space, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Education Inter-Institutional Study Ball State Teachers College, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Education Biennial Budget Request-Operating Budget Request, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Education Salaries, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Education Faculty-Student Ratio Study of Four Schools, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Education Faculty Studies, degrees, etc, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Education Degrees Granted, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Student Fees, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Budget Medical Center Building Needs, 1953-1955 -; 1952-1953 (Box 95)
    - Morning Folder, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Thank you letters, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Free hafer coves re formula, 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Budget Other Schools, 1952-1953- (Box 95)
  - BudgetOther Schools, 1953-1955-; 1952-1953 (Box 95)
  - Budget Report, 1952-1953; (4 folders) (Box 95)
  - Budget, 1953-1954; (2 folders) (Box 95)
  - Classroom Utilization Fall, 1953-1954 (Box 95)
  - Budget-Biennial Budget Request, 1953-1955; (2 folders) (Box 95)
  - Capital Outlay, 1953-1954 (Box 95)
  - Budget, 1953-1954; (2 folders) (Box 95)
  - Budget, 1954-1955; (5 folders) (Box 95)
  - Requests to State Budget Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 95)
  - Budget, Biennial Budget Request, 1955-1957; (4 folders) (Box 95)
  - Budget, 1955-1957 (Box 95)
  - Budget Report to State CommitteeIndiana University, July 1954 (Box 96)
  - Budget Biennial Budget Request, 1955-1957; (15 folders) (Box 96)
  - Budget-Biennium, 1955-1957 (Box 96)
    - Capital Request, July 15, 1954 (Box 96)
    - Request-Operating (Box 96)
    - Miscellaneous, 1955-1956 (Box 96)
    - Appreciation Letters, 1955-1956 (Box 96)
    - Departmental Salaries, etc., 1955-1956 (Box 96)
    - Supporting Papers, 1955-1956 (Box 96)
    - Other Schools, 1955-1956 (Box 96)
    - Biennial Budget RequestGeneral Legislative Request Information, 1955-1957- (Box 96)
    - Committee Meeting, March 23, 1956 (Box 96)
    - Work Papers and Correspondence Other Than General Fund, 1955-1956 (Box 96)
    - Work Papers, Correspondence, details etc., 1955-1956 (Box 96)
    - Biennial Budget Request, 1955-1957 (Box 96)
    - Construction-State Financing Pay as you go, 1955-1956 (Box 96)
  - Economic Future, 1955-1956 (Box 96)
  - Legislature-Out of State Fees, 1955-1956 (Box 96)
  - Budget Request-Capital, 1955-1956 (Box 96)
  - Budget, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Appreciation Letters (Box 97)
    - Departmental Requests (Box 97)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 97)
    - Appreciation Letters (Box 97)
    - Other Schools (Box 97)
    - Supporting Papers (Box 97)
  - Budget Biennial Budget Request Miscellaneous, 1957-1959; 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Adult Education Center, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Appreciation Letters, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Dean Briscoe's Folder, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Capital, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Operating, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Committee Meeting, March 26, 1956 (Box 97)
    - Four State Schools Meeting, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Prints of Charts, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Geological Survey, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - President Wells' Legislative Folder (Duplicate), 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - The Crucial Decade, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Report on the College Faculty Problem, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Economic Forecast for Fiscal Years, 1957; 1958; and 1959 (Box 97)
    - Operating Requests-State Colleges and Universities (Box 97)
    - Facts Underlying Operating Requirements, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Four State Schools Legislative Request for Operation, 1957-1959 (Box 97)
    - Four State Schools Operating Request Basis, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Indiana University Legislative Budget Request, 1957-1959 (Box 97)
    - Four State Schools Legislative Requests for Capital, 1957-1959 (Box 97)
    - Basic Student Fee Comparison-Big Ten State Schools (Box 97)
    - Student Fees-Big Ten State Universities, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Indiana University Building, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
    - Dormitory Rates-Big Ten Schools, 1957-1958 (Box 97)
  - Budget Committee Visit-Medical Center, March 7, 1956 (Box 97)
  - Budget, 1957-1959 (Box 97)
  - Budget Conferences, 1956-1957 (Box 97)
  - Budget Other Schools, 1957-1958- (Box 97)
    - Appreciation Letters (Box 97)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 97)
  - Budget Request Planning, 1957-1958 (Box 97)
  - Budget Supporting Papers, 1957-1958- (Box 97)
  - Budget-Biennial Budget Request, 1957-1959 (Box 97)
  - Budget (Box 97)
  - Budget, 1958 (Box 97)
  - Budget, 1958-1959 (Box 97)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 97)
    - Appreciation Letters (Box 97)
    - Other Schools (Box 97)
    - Supporting Papers (Box 97)
  - Budget, 1958-1959 (Box 97)
    - Working papers from the Dean of Faculties (Box 97)
  - Budget, 1958-1959 (Box 98)
  - Biennial Budget RequestIndex, 1959-1961- (Box 98)
    - Appropriation requests for construction, rehabilitaion, and repair, July 7, 1958 (Box 98)
    - Appropriation requests by Ball State, October 1, 1958 (Box 98)
    - Operating appropriation request by Four State Schools, September 29, 1956 (Box 98)
    - Appropriation Requests by Four State Schools, October 1, 1958 (Box 98)
    - Data on Faculty Salaries (Box 98)
    - Data on Student Fees (Box 98)
    - Data on Enrollment (Box 98)
    - Data on Degrees Conferred (Box 98)
    - Data on Construction and the Physical Plant (Box 98)
    - Publications re the Cost of Higher Education in Indiana (Box 98)
    - Data on the Indianapolis and Medical Center (Box 98)
    - Data on Four State School Study and Appropriation Request (Box 98)
    - Papers on the Internal Budget (Box 98)
    - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 98)
    - Materials on the Problem of Duplication (Box 98)
    - Materials on the Franke Resolution (Box 98)
    - Data on State Legislative and Executive Personnel and Action (Box 98)
    - Materials for Meeting of Governor and State College and University Presidents (Box 98)
    - Papers Used in Wells' Meeting with State Budget Committee, June 20, 1958 (Box 98)
    - Appreciation Letters (Box 98)
  - Legislative Budget RequestsPackets of printed material, 1959-1961- (Box 98)
  - Biennial Budget Request, 1959-1961 (Box 98)
    - Indiana Legislative Directory (Box 98)
  - Legislative Budget Request for the Biennium, 1959-1961 (Box 98)
  - Biennial Budget RequestLegislative Action to Date on Bills of Interest to Indiana University, 1959-1961- (Box 98)
  - BudgetMiscellaneous, 1959-1960 - (Box 98)
  - Budget Material to Work Up (Box 98)
  - BudgetSupporting Papers, 1959-1960- (Box 98)
    - Appreciation Letters (Box 98)
    - Other Schools (Box 98)
    - Supporting Papers (Box 98)
    - Treasurer's Office (Box 98)
  - Budget Biennial Budget Request, 1958-1960 (Box 98)
    - Appreciation Letters (Box 98)
  - Budget Miscellaneous, 1960-1961- (Box 98)
  - Budget, 1960-1961 (Box 98)
    - Appreciation Letters (Box 98)
    - Other Schools (Box 98)
    - Supporting Papers (Box 98)
  - Budget Biennial Budget Request, 1963-1965 (Box 98)
  - Budget Biennial Budget Request, 1961-1963 (Box 98)
    - Capital Request, 1960-1961 (Box 98)
    - Four State Schools' 10-Year Building Needs Study (Box 98)
    - Mailing list for letter regarding Construction and Operating Requests, 1960-1961 (Box 98)
    - Operating Request Summary, 1960-1961 (Box 98)
  - BudgetMiscellaneous, 1961-1962- (Box 98)
    - Appreciation Letters (Box 98)
    - Other Schools (Box 98)
    - Supporting Papers (Box 98)
  - Budget Biennial Budget Request, 1963-1965 (Box 98)
    - Appreciation Letters (Box 98)
  - Bue, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 99)
  - Bui, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 99)
  - Buffalo, University of Buffalo, N.Y., 1937-1944; (7 folders) (Box 99)
  - Building Costs - Indianapolis Medical Center (Box 99)
  - Buildings, 1937-1940; (3 folders) (Box 99)
  - Buildings - RE: Naming of I.U. Blue Key to Sponsor, 1939-1940 (Box 99)
  - Buildings RE: Keeping them open after midnight and on Sunday, 1939-1940 (Box 99)
  - Buildings, 1940-1944; (4 folders) (Box 99)
  - Buildings - Miscellaneous Statistics on, 1937-1938 (Box 99)
    - Names-Letters to Families (Box 99)
    - Additions to Physical Plant at I.U. (Box 99)
  - Building Program-Meeting of Four State Schools, Oct. 18, 1945 (Box 99)
    - Press Release (Box 99)
  - Buildings-P.W.A. (Box 99)
  - Building Program Report for Tentative P.W.A. aplications Add. to Union Bldg., Dormitories and Class Room Building, 1937-1938 (Box 99)
  - Buildings, 1946 (Box 99)
  - Building Program-Letters of appreciation to contractors, etc, 1946 (Box 99)
  - Buildings, 1944-1945 (Box 99)
  - Building Program, 1945-1946 (Box 99)
  - Buildings, 1946-1952; (6 folders) (Box 99)
  - Building Costs (Box 99)
  - Buildings-Myers Hall, naming ceremony (Box 99)
    - Square Footage (Box 99)
    - Use, 1951-1956 (Box 99)
  - Buildings and Grounds Department-five year report, 1943 (Box 99)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1952-1956; (5 folders) (Box 99)
  - Buildings and Grounds-Treasurer's Folder, 1956-1959; (2 folders) (Box 100)
  - Buildings and Grounds Service Fund, 1949-1959; (9 folders) (Box 100)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1959-1960; (2 folders) (Box 100)